http://www.frederick.edu/policies-terms-of-use/disclaimer.aspx

Menu
Search
Tools & Resources
Arts Center
¡Bienvenidos!
Staff Directory
search:
Arts
¡Bienvenidos!
myFCC
search:
Arts
¡Bienvenidos!
Disclaimer and Privacy Policy
The information contained in this website is for general information purposes. Although the college strives to keep information on the website up-to-date and correct, we cannot guarantee that it will be so. As a result, the college makes no representations or warranties of any kind, either express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability, or availability of either the website itself or the information, products, or services provided on it. The viewer to the website is responsible for contacting the appropriate college office to verify information, and any reliance that the visitor to the website may place on the information, products, or services provided on the website is, therefore, strictly at his or her own risk.
In no event will the college be liable for any loss or damage whatsoever that may arise in connection with the use of this website.
Through this website, the viewer may be able to link to other websites that are not under the control of the college. The existence of these links does not suggest that the college approves, recommends, or endorses the content of those websites.
Privacy Policy
Frederick Community College officials have created this privacy policy statement to demonstrate their commitment to privacy. FCC recognizes and respects the importance of responsible use of your personal information. FCC collects information volunteered by you on this website primarily to provide you with relevant information and updates regarding FCC programs and services.
We will not sell or disclose to unrelated third parties any personally-identifiable information you volunteer on this website. In addition to collecting information volunteered by you on our website, our server logs aggregate information on visitor IP addresses and pages accessed.
Cookies: Our website may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our website. A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored and later retrieved by a website. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set it. You can configure your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our website will not function properly when you view them.
Email Data: FCC may use your email address to send correspondence about information you have requested, important updates, and newsletters. Your Acceptance to These Terms: By using this site, you signify your consent to the Frederick.edu Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the FCC website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting to the frederick.edu website.
7932 Opossumtown Pike Frederick, MD 21702
301.846.2400 · Copyright © 2020
Contact Us
Directions & Maps
Hours of Operation
College Security
Doing Business with FCC
Employment
Frederick Community College prohibits discrimination against any person on the basis of age, ancestry, citizenship status, color, creed,
ethnicity, gender identity and expression, genetic information, marital status, mental or physical disability, national origin, race,
religious affiliation, sex, sexual orientation, or veteran status in its activities, admissions, educational programs, and employment.
